

DAMIEN BOUVET

WEB DEVELOPER

+33 6 37 30 69 43 codindb.com damien.bouvet@gmail.com 36 years old, Chavanod (Fr)

"I invest myself alongside entrepreneurs and project owners, in order to create, maintain or improve their web applications

As a front-end developer, passionate about web development, I'd love to help you achieve your goals. "



SOFT SKILLS

Intellectual curiosity

Abnegation

Teamwork

Adaptability

Eagerness to learn

HARD SKILLS

HTML SCSS Javascript

Vue.js Firebase Strapi

Git VS Code Scrum



EXPERIENCES

Freelance Web Developer 2021 - Present

Front-end Developer 2020 - 2021

Quasar Solutions / Obilog , Annecy (Fr)



More details? → https://codindb.com/#experience

EDUCATION

Campus Numérique in the Alps

2019 - 2021

Formation de Technicien Développeur Titre RNCP Niveau 5

Western Carolina University - USA

2003 - 2007

Bachelor of Science in Sport Management

MISC.

Basketball



Cinema



Motorcycle





